嘿
Hey.
怎么了  搭地铁时有人舔我的脖子
What's the matter? Someone on the subway licked my neck!
舔我的脖子  威利还活着
Licked my neck! Whoa! Willy's still alive.
你们在做什么   我妈打电话来
What are you guys doing? My mom called.
他们要登报通知亲友  我们要订婚了
They're gonna run our engagement announcement in the local paper.
我们想找张漂亮的合影   怕是不可能啊
so we're looking for a good picture of us. Ooh, I'm afraid that does not exist.
我们合拍了很多不错的照片
That's not true, There are great pictures of us.
不  你照得很好  但你旁边的男人是这样的
No, there are great pictures of you standing next to a guy who's going like this...
天啊  他就是在自由女神像旁  跟你合照的怪胎
Oh, my God, that's the creep that you're with at the Statue of Liberty.
我不知道这是怎么一回事   我就没办法好好照相
I don't know what it is. I just can't take a good picture.
这一张很不错
Oh, here's a great one.
对  那张没有我  没错  但我全身晒得黑亮
Yeah, I'm not in that. No, I know, but look at me, all tan.
你们为什么不请专业摄影师  帮你们拍照呢
Why don't you guys go, get portraits done by a professional photographer?
好点子   我敢说他们一定有大风扇
That's a great idea. I bet they have one of those wind machines, Y'know.
那的确很棒  真的那么做的话  钱德应该看起来不会这么蠢
Yeah, that's great. Next to that, Chandler won't look so stupid.
钱德  你觉得呢  没问题  但我得警告你
Chandler, what do you say? All right, but I should warn you.
我不去   "我"会去
I'm not going. I'm going.
老友记   第七季  第05集  订婚照
Friends  S07E05  The One With The Engagement Picture
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
兄弟  那一记反手投篮帅呆了
Dude, that reverse lay-up. Ugh!
那些三分球呢   太棒了
And how about those three-pointers? Amazing.
这次也是就差这么一点   那些家伙就答应让我们上场了
And those guys were this close to letting us play this time too.
你们看  菲比在跟咖啡厅帅哥说话
Hey, look. Phoebe's talking to Cute Coffeehouse Guy.
你叫他 "咖啡厅帅哥"吗   我们叫他"边尿边哼歌先生"
Oh, you guys call him "Cute Coffeehouse Guy"? We call him "Hums While He Pees."
对  我们叫罗斯  "厕所里逗留男"
Yes, and we call Ross "Lingers in the Bathroom."
大伙们  "边尿边哼歌先生"   刚刚约我出去
Hey, you guys, "Hums While He Pees" just asked me out.
我以为他结婚了  没错   但他正在办离婚
I thought that guy was married. He is, but he's getting divorced.
罗斯  或许你认识他
Ross, maybe you know him.
这又不是俱乐部
It's not a club.
菲比  如果他正在办离婚   你觉得跟他约会适当吗
Phoebe, If this guy's going through a divorce, is it such a good idea to start going out with him?
离婚男人又不是坏男人
Hey, divorced men are not bad men.
他们把那句话印在俱乐部的纸巾上了
They have that on the napkins at the club.
我得回去上班了  你还可以休息半小时
Oh, I gotta get back to work. You don't have to be back for a half-hour.
但是我的助理泰格午餐时间里  会在办公室做仰卧起坐
Yeah but, My assistant, Tag, does sit-ups in the office during lunch. Heh.
我真的快被他迷死了
Ugh, I could just spread him on a cracker.
你在暗恋他  为什么还要雇用他
Rach, if you have a crush on this guy, why would you hire him?
你知道你不能跟他约会  对吧  对啊  我知道
I mean you know you can't date him, right? Oh, no, I know that.
我们开玩笑说  因为我们常常在一起
Although we made a joke that we spend so much time together...
他应该叫我 "工作上的太太"
...he should call me his "work-wife."
很快地  他就可以叫你 "那个被开除的女人"
Soon he'll be able to call you "that lady he knew that got fired."
我不会被开除   因为我不会采取行动
I'm not gonna get fired, because I'm not gonna act on it.
你不会介意   他跟别人约会吧
So you wouldn't mind if he was dating someone else?
怎么了  他有吗  他有  对吧  他跟行销部那个荡妇约会
Why, is he? He is, isn't he? He's dating that slut in marketing.
或许我该成立一个离婚男子俱乐部
Maybe I should open a divorced men's club.
兄弟  那太惨了
Dude, that's so sad.
我会在后院设一个篮球场
I could put a basketball court in the back. Heh.
我能下场打球吗
Could I play?
你今天不做仰卧起坐吗   泰格
Oh, no sit-ups today, Tag?
我做完了   再给我做十下吧
I just did them. Oh, well, drop and give me 1O more. Heh.
什么
What?
我午餐喝了酒   那些
I had a drink with lunch. Did those, um--?
成本报告送过来了吗   我昨晚就已经归档了
Did those cost reports come in? Yeah, I filled them out last night.
很好  麻烦你帮我复印四份
Oh, great. Could you make me 4 copies of those?
没问题  太棒了  谢谢你
Sure. Great, thank you.
嗨  端秋  嗨  梅丽莎  有什么事吗
Hey, Rachel. Hi. Hi, Melissa. What's up?
我正好要出去血拼
I'm just about to, urn, go out to the store.
想买些东西放进我的背包里
to get some stuff to put in my backpack.
像水果干  速食麦片  那一类的东西
You know, like dried fruit and granola, and stuff like that.
有什么事吗   秦格在吗
Um, what's up? ls Tag here?
他不在  怎么了  我要来问他
No. Why? Oh, I was gonna talk to him...
今晚要不要跟我出去  真的吗
...about doing something tonight. Really?
你喜欢泰格  对吧
You got a little crush on Tag there, do you?
我们一直都在眉目传情的
Well, we've been flirting back and forth...
但我希望今晚   事情能有点进展
...but I was hoping that tonight it would turn into something a little more than that.
别猴急  梅丽莎  这里不是更衣室
Okay, whoa, whoa. Easy there, Melissa. This ain't a locker room, okay.
但我记得他说过   今晚他已经有约了
But you know, I remember him saying that he had plans tonight.
不  没错
Oh, no. Oh, yeah.
好吧  快回去工作
Oh yeah. All right, back to work.
那不是泰格的背包吗
Hey, isn't that Tag's backpack?
我不想当办公室里的臭女人
Yeah, Melissa, I don't want to be known as the, uh, office bitch...
但我会打电话给你主管
...but I will call your supervisor.
太棒了  非常不错  摩妮卡  很好
Great, that's great, Monica. Great.
好了  钱德   你能笑一个吗
Now, Chandler, you want to give us a smile?
好吧
0Kay.
对不起  那张椅子很不舒服吗  不  是我很不舒服
I'm sorry, is the seat uncomfortable? No, I am.
钱德  我知道你办得到   你笑起来很帅的
Chandler, I know you can do this. Okay? You have a beautiful smile.
是吗  没错
I do? Yeah.
或许你不必笑   我们来试试别的点子   试着
All right, maybe you don't have to smile. Let's try something else. Let's try, um--
试着表现出性感的样子  好吧
Try looking sexy. Okay.
还是不要吧
Or not.
乔伊  你在这里做什么
Hi, Joey, what are you doing here?
我要在附近试镜   结果酱汁沾到衣服上了
I got an audition down the street, and I spilled sauce all over my shirt.
你有多余的衬衫吗  当然有
You got an extra one? Yeah, sure. Um...
拿去吧
Here.
太棒了
Great.
你有除了罗夫罗兰外   其他品牌的衣服吗
You got anything that's not Ralph Lauren?
应该没有  乔伊
Yeah, I don't think so, Joe.
好吧  我猜这件应该可以
All right, I guess this'll be fine.
你今晚要做什么   没事  怎么了
Hey, Listen, uh, what are you doing tonight? Nothing. Why?
你要不要带我的助理泰格   出去玩
How would you feel about taking out my assistant Tag?
我付钱
I'll pay. Heh.
要我跟男人出去约会  可得付我一大笔钱
Huh, Rach I got to say it's gonna take a lot of money for me to go out on a date with a dude.
我不是要你跟他约会
I'm not asking you to go on a date with him.
真的吗   因为我真的很缺钱
Really? Because I could kind of use the money.
乔伊  他刚搬到这里来  我知道他没有男性朋友
Joey, just-He's new in town and he doesn't have any guy friends.
带他去看看球赛或做点别的事  我会非常感激你
Just take him to a ball game or something. I'd appreciate it.
好的  没问题  谢谢你
Yeah, okay, no problem. Thank you.
是甜甜圈
Ooh, hey, doughnuts! Uh-huh.
我知道  我们来试试看
I know. Let's try a look...
出神的表情
...of far-off wonderment.
凝视我们的未来  想想我们的婚姻跟以后的日子
Okay, we'll-we'll gaze into our future and we'll think about our marriage and the days to come.
钱德  你的脸到底是怎么了
Chandler, what is the matter with your face?
这张照片应该要表达   "盖勒和宾府喜事"的
I mean this picture's supposed to say "Geller and Bing to be married"...
不是"英勇女市民  救了快淹死的蠢蛋"
...not "Local woman saves drowning moron."
嘿   别笑他
Ha-ha-ha. Hey, don't laugh at him.
这个快淹死的蠢蛋是我的
He's my drowning moron.
对了  就是这样  快拍下来
Aw. That's it, that's it! Take it, take it!
（中央咖啡厅）
我喜欢这一张
I like this one.
它似乎是在说  "我爱你  所以我要杀了你"
It seems to say, "I love you and that's why I have to kill you."
不会全部都那么糟糕啦
They can't all be bad.
找那张你装出  睡眼朦胧的照片
Find the one where you make your bedroom eyes.
我找到了
Oh, there it is.
我的天啊   这就是我睡眼朦胧的样子
Oh, my God, those are my bedroom eyes?
你为什么要跟我同床共枕
Why did you ever sleep with me?
你真的想提这件事情吗
Do you really want to pull at that thread?
我真的玩得很开心  我也是
I'm having a really good time. Me too.
很抱歉地铁里那个家伙  舔了你的脖子
Sorry that guy on the subway licked your neck.
不  没关系  他是朋友
No, that's okay. He's a friend.
恕我放肆
Uh, I don't mean to be presumptuous...
但我有明天国标舞总决赛的门票  如果你想去的话
...but I have these two tickets to the ballroom-dancing finals tomorrow night if you want to go?
对  我
Yeah, I--
我没有看准决赛  我想我看不懂
Well y'know I-I mean I missed the semi-finals, so I think I would just be lost.
我知道那样真的很无聊   但这些票是我的老板
Heh, I know that it's lame, but I got these tickets from my boss--
喔  不  我的天啊
Oh, no, no, no, my God!
好了  别大惊小怪的   我去就是了  不
Okay, don't freak out. I'll go. No, it's--
是我的前妻惠特妮
My ex-wife Whitney is out there.
我现在没办法面对她   那个女人疯了
I cannot deal with her now. That woman is crazy.
好吧  我知道  等一下
Okay, I know. Hold on.
嘿   罗斯  什么事
Hey, Ross. Yeah.
凯尔的前妻  惠特妮就在外面
Yeah. Urn, that's Whitney, Kyle's ex-wife out there.
你可以把她诱开   让我们脱身吗
Do you think that you can y'know divert her so that we can slip out?
什么  不
What? No.
好吧  但我有两张国标舞总决赛的门票
Okay, but I have two tickets to the ballroom-dance finals.
我想还是不要吧   菲比
Look, I don't think so, Pheebs. I, heh--
好吧   我愿意
All right, I'll do it.
但那只是因为你是我的朋友   好吧
But just because you're a friend. Okay.
嗨  大舞王
Hi, Ginger.
我要拿回我的钥匙
All right! I want my key back.
我没拿  钥匙就那里
I don't have it. It's right there.
好吧  大侦探福尔摩斯
Ugh. Okay, Sherlock.
对不起  但你最好快点离开   菲比
Look, I'm sorry, but you'd better go, Pheebs.
我只是要谢谢你   帮我们诱开凯尔的前妻
All right. I just wanted to thank you though for diverting Kyle's ex.
别客气  待会再谈
Oh, yeah, no, you're welcome. We'll, uh, talk about it later.
好
Okay. Heh.
嗨  惠特妮   嗨   罗斯
Hi, Whitney. Hi, Ross.
你准备好要去吃早餐了吗   是的
Are you ready for breakfast? Yep. Ooh.
凯尔的前妻你应该要诱开她  不是跟她约会
Kyle's ex-wife? You were supposed to divert her, not date her.
你能不能等我一下  我得跟这个女人谈一谈
Sorry, can you give me a second while I talk to this woman...
顺便一提  她没有在这里过夜
...uh, who, by the way, did not spend the night?
没问题   好吧
Sure. Okay. Eh, heh...
我的确诱开她了  后来我们玩得很开心   好吗
I did divert her, and we ended up having a great time, okay?
你们一起去看国标舞比赛   对啊
Watching ballroom dancing? Yes.
那时我们发现  事实上我们俩都酷呆了
That's where we realized we are both super cool people.
听着  罗斯  凯尔告诉我  她有些很差劲的缺点
Look, okay, Ross. Kyle just told me some really bad stuff about her.
譬如说呢   譬如说她很无情
Like what? Like she's really mean.
她喜欢吹毛求疵
And she's overly critical and-And-No.
她会不经过你的同意   就把房间刷成很明亮的颜色
She will paint a room a really bright color without even checking with you.
好吧
0Kay.
她还会把性当成武器
And she uses sex as a weapon.
谢谢你的警告
Fine. Thank you for warning me.
早餐时我会注意   油漆跟性武器
At breakfast, I'll be on full alert for room painting and sex weapons.
你还是要跟她约会  对
You're still gonna go outwith her? Yeah.
你没有听到  刚刚我说的话吗
Well, didn't you hear what I just said?
菲比  少来了  你的消息来源有问题
Pheebs, come on. I mean, consider the source.
她的前夫当然会那么说   请你离开了啦
Of course her ex-husband's gonna say that stuff. Now if you'll excuse me.
听我说   她疯了
No, listen to me, she is crazy!
你的门没有隔音功能
Uh, your door isn't sound proof.
看到了吧   她就是爱挑剔
You see? Nothing is good enough for her.
早安  嗨  泰格
Morning. Hi, Tag.
昨晚你跟乔伊玩得开心吗
Hey, so did you have fun with, uh, Joey last night?
对  我们去看《尼克队》比赛
Yeah, we went to the Knicks game.
真的太棒了
Aw, that's nice.
然后我们去酒吧玩   他帮我们泡上好多女人
Then we went to this bar, and he hooked us up with all these women.
女人  你是说老女人
Women? You mean, like old women?
有点老  大概三十岁
Kind of old, like 30.
是喔  我以前没办法
Oh. And I never used to be able...
在酒吧里跟女人聊天
...to just talk to girls in bars...
但昨晚我就拿到了  二十个电话号码
...but I got, like, 20 phone numbers last night.
真的是太棒了
That's great.
乔伊真的教会你一些事
Oh, man. So Joey must have really taught you some stuff.
没错  是啊
A little. Yeah.
你好吗
How you doing?
看吧  那个笑容非常灿烂   轻松  自然
See? That's a great smile. Easy, natural.
现在假装我手上拿了照相机
Now pretend I have a camera.
你的笑容变了  我控制不了自己
You're changing it. I can't help it.
好吧  你想知道  我都是怎么拍沙龙照的吗
All right. all right, You want to know what I do when I take resume shots?
你跟我借钱
Borrow money from me?
对  好吧  首先  你得装出自然的样子
Yeah. Okay, first of all, you want to make it look spontaneous.
我都是这么做的  我会低头  低头  继续低头
So here's what I do. I look down, look down, keep looking down.
然后抬头
Then I look up.
看到没  现在你来试试看
See? All right, now you try.
低头  低头  继续低头
Look down. You're looking down. Keep looking down.
你的鞋子上为什么会有果酱
Why is there jelly on your shoe?
我吃了甜甜圈   是喔
I had a doughnut. Oh.
嗨  嘿
Hi. Hey.
听说昨晚你跟泰格玩得很开心
So, I heard you had some fun with Tag last night.
对  那家伙还不错
Yeah, that guy's all right.
对  你很高兴教他怎么当 "乔伊"
Yeah, and you had fun teaching him how to be all "Joey."
什么  你知道的  泡马子
What? You know, all the women.
你没办法教别人怎么泡马子
Hey well, You can't teach someone to be good with women.
所以我跟钱德出去  老是泡不到马子
Y'know, That's why I never had any luck with Chandler.
我在这里啊
I'm right here.
你能不能别再跟他一起出去了
All right, Would you mind just not going outwith him again?
就是你跟他一起去泡马子
Okay, just the idea of you and he and all these women--it's just
我知道他是我的助理   我不能跟他约会
And I know he's my assistant, and I can't date him, blah!
但这真的让我很困扰   好吗
but it just bothers me, all right?
不  你不能抢走他
No, no, no, you can't take him away from me.
我终于找到一个  可以跟我一起去泡马子的拍档了
I got a great partner to pick up girls with. Finally!
我还在这里啊
I'm still right here.
至少你可以跟他谈一谈
All right, will you at least talk to him...
告诉他跟一大堆女人约会   既空虚又得不到满足
...and tell him how hollow and unsatisfying this dating-tons-of-women thing is?
什么
What?
在我结束对他的暗恋之前  我不要他跟任何人约会
I just don't want him to meet anybody until I'm over my crush.
我会忘记他的
And I will get over it.
我并不爱他  那只是肉体上的吸引力
It's not like I love him. It's just physical.
我常常这样暗恋男人   刚认识你时我就暗恋过你
But—I mean I get these crushes all the time. Hell, I had a crush on you when I met you.
我知道  摩妮卡跟我说过
I know. Monica told me.
我们刚认识时  你暗恋过我吗
Did you have a crush on me when you first met me?
对  有啊
Yeah, sure.
难道你们就是看不到我吗
Can you people not see me?
你能跟他谈谈吗
So will you talk to him?
我不知道  瑞秋  我会送你十件罗夫罗兰的衬衫
I don't know, Rach. Oh, come on! I'll give you 10 Ralph Lauren shirts.
一件
One.
不   十件   你说十件   你不能反悔
No, 10. You said 10. You can't take that back.
（中央咖啡厅）
嘿   你有事要跟我谈
Hey Joey, You wanted to talk to me?
我不知道   你拿了东西来给我吗
I don't know. You, uh, got something for me?
对  这是端秋要给你的
Oh, yeah, this is from Rachel.
十件  好吧
Ten. Okay.
泰格  跟太多女人约会下场是不好的
Tag, there's such a thing as too many women.
真的吗   对你来说是的
Really? Yeah, for you.
嘿   你来了  我来了
Hey, there you are. There I am.
你没事吧   没事   乔伊说我需要放轻松
You okay? Yeah, Joey said I, uh, needed to relax.
他给我吃抗组脐药
So he gave me an antihistamine.
什么  对啊
What? Yeah.
我搭地铁时睡着了  结果到了布鲁克林
and then I fell asleep on the subway and went to Brooklyn.
布鲁克林好远
Brooklyn is far.
你在想什么
Chandler, What were you thinking?
我不知道  别担心  因为现在我知道要怎么拍照了
I don't know, But don't worry, because I know how to take a picture now.
好了  看吧  低头
Okay, see. Look down.
低头
Look down.
钱德  什么事
Chandler? Yeah?
嗨  嗨
Hi. Hi.
你跟疯婆子还好吧   她把你的兔子拿去煮了吗
So how are things going with Crazy? Has she cooked your rabbit yet?
听着  你只听到片面之词  好吗
Listen, you are hearing one side of the story. Okay?
还有  她拿了三十份   油漆样本给凯尔看
and FYI, she must have shown Kyle over 30 paint samples...
之后才动手漆房间的
...before she painted that room.
他对每一份样本的反应是  "我一点都不在乎"
And his response to each one was, "I don't give a tiny rat's ass."
或许她该少花点时间在装修上
Yeah well, maybe she should have spent a little less time decorating...
多花一点时间在卧室里
...and a little more time in the bedroom.
我想我们不会有那样的问题吧
Well, I don't think we are going to have that problem...
但或许那是因为  我不会吝于付出感情
...but maybe that's just because I am not emotionally unavailable.
你认为他吝于付出感情
You think he's emotionally unavailable?
我想有那个可能
I think he can be.
如果她没有
Well, Maybe he wouldn't be...
每晚把公事带回家做  或许他就不会那样子
...if she didn't bring the office home every night.
你得原谅她   知道该怎么面对她的生活
Well excuse her for knowing what she wants to do with her life.
她的确知道  她在1997年除夕做了什么
Well, she certainly knew what she was doing New Year's Eve 1997.
我就知道你会那么说
I knew you were gonna throw that in my face!
那是三年前的事  她一再地道歉
That was three years ago. She apologized and apologized.
你还想怎么样
What more do you want?
我们要找回六年的时光
We want the last six years back!
我们也是  我们也是
So do we! So do we!
很抱歉  让你们看到这一幕
I'm sorry you had to see that.
早安  端秋  嗨
Morning, Rachel. Hi.
昨晚你做了什么
Hey, so, uh, what'd you do last night?
我跟乔伊出去了  是吗
Went out with Joey. Oh, yeah?
你们又去泡妞了
Another night of bird-dogging the chicas?
不  我们坐下来长谈
No, we had a really good talk. Oh.
我想我不会  再去酒吧泡女人了
I don't think I'm gonna do that bar scene anymore.
我没想到你会那么说
Wow, I did not see that coming.
那不是真正的我
It's just not really who I am.
我一直都很快乐  当
Y'know, I've always been happier when--
我为什么要告诉你这件事
Why am I telling you this?
你不会关心这种事  不  我很关心
You don't care about this stuff. Yes, I do. I do.
刚刚你说  "我一直都很快乐  当"
Go on. You were saying, "I'm happier when I'm--"
当我谈恋爱时
When I'm in a relationship.
我喜欢女朋友陪在身边  真的吗
I love having a girlfriend. Really?
我可以好好宠爱她
Yeah. Someone I can spoil, you know.
宠爱
Sp-Spoil? Uh-huh.
我要问你一件事
Let me ask you something. Uh-huh?
你相信我们都在寻找另一半吗
Do you believe there's one perfect person for everyone?
我开始相信了
I'm starting to.
如果那个人已经出现在你的生命中   你应该努力去争取吗
And if that person's in your life, you should do something about it?
对  当然
Yes. Hell, yes.
好吧  那么我就安心了
All right, then, it's settled. Okay.
我要跟我前女友复合   我愿意
I'm getting back together with my ex. I would love to!
什么
What?
喂
Hello?
我应该会谈上一阵子  对不起
Oh. This is gonna be a while. Excuse me.
对
Um, yeah.
Yeah.
我的天啊
My God!
对不起   吵到你了吗
Oh, I'm sorry. Is that annoying?
说到在床上很自私   惠特妮还好吗
And speaking of being selfish in bed, how's Whitney?
或许她不必在床上很自私
Well maybe she wouldn't have to be selfish in bed...
如果另一个人知道  哪里是哪里
...if someone else knew where everything was.
他的确知道
Oh, he knows. Heh.
大部份啦
For the most part.
嘿  太好了  你们两个都在
Oh, hey. Good, you're both here.
我们得谈一谈
We kind of need to talk.
你们两个在一起  怎么了
Both of you together? What's up?
昨晚我到凯尔家   拿一些东西
Well, I went over to Kyle's last night to pick up a few things...
我们回忆了一些往事
...and we got to reminiscing.
几乎谈了一整个晚上
We talked most of the night...
我们明白  我们会这么气对方
...and we realized the reason we're angry with each other...
是因为我们还对彼此有感觉
...is because there are still feelings there.
所以
So...
喔  快说吧  凯尔
Oh, just say it, Kyle!
我们要再试一次
We're gonna give it another try.
你不是说她爱抱怨   常常要人注意她吗
What about her whining, and her constant need for attention?
我会努力调整自己
I'm gonna work on that.
对  因为你很善变
Oh, right, because you're so capable of change.
你知道的  他会边尿边哼歌
You know, he hums when he pees.
我知道  所以他都尿不准   但那不重要
I do know. Makes him miss the bowl, but whatever.
我们很抱歉
We're so sorry.
没关系   我们不需要你们  我已经忘了这件事
That's all right. We don't need you. I'm over it already.
对  我根本一点都不在乎
Yeah, and I don't even give a tiny rat's ass.
我们得走了
Yeah, we're gonna go.
对不起
I'm sorry.
菲比  你没有看错她
Pheebs, you were right about her.
她的确试图把性当成武器
You know, she did try to use sex as a weapon.
我的背有一点痛
Yeah, I hurt my back a little.
他做其他事时  也会哼歌
You know, he hums while he does other stuff too.
没有他们  我们能过得更好
We're better off without them. Heh.
就算他们再分手  千万别让他加入你的什么伤心男子俱乐部
And y'know, Even if they break up again, you better not let him in your sad men's club.
是离婚男人俱乐部   有什么不一样呢
Divorced men's club. Potato, "potato."
大家快来看
Hey, guys, check it out.
我妈把报纸寄给我   我们来瞧瞧
My morn sent me the paper. Ooh, let's see it. Yay.
看起来不错   你们看起来很配啊
Oh, yeah, that looks good. You guys make a very attractive couple.
对  我们是天生一对   一点都没错
Yeah, we look great together. We really do.
好吧
0Kay.
想像一下我们的孩子会是什么模样
Imagine what our kids would look like.
我们不必想像
You know, we don't have to imagine.
我要娶她
I'm marrying her.
走着瞧吧
We'll just see.